Hello everyone, this is Stephen as
usual. So, we are currently at a
critical juncture in DSX's IPO process,
so which directly impacts the subsequent
use and fund security of every member's
account first of all. So, first I want
to confirm a key piece of information.
So, DSX right now has officially entered
the crucial stage of IPO preparation and
has introduced a relevant auditing
department to conduct a systematic
review for the entire platform. So, this
review is not just a simple procedure,
so but a very rigorous auditing
mechanism. So, so far focusing on three
core areas. So, first is the accuracy of
the financial statements,
second the clarity of fund flows, and
the third one
whether all account data complies with a
capital market compliance standards,
right? So, Well, in other words, DSX
has now officially moved from
internal development phase to phase of
being reviewed and verified. So,
however,
a very critical issue has
arisen during the audit process.
The auditing department discovered
irregularities
in the use of some accounts,
particularly as a practice of one person
holding multiple accounts. That's
unfortunate, of course. So, this
not only affects the accuracy of the
data, but also involves unclear account
ownership and ambiguous
tax responsibilities, of course.
So, more seriously, according to
current statistics, this situation
accounts for
over 70% of cases and is
distributed across various teams.
What does this mean?
This means the overall compliance of the
platform data has been affected. So, for
this reason, the review process has been
temporarily suspended.
The review department has clearly
stated that comprehensive
restrictions must be complete before the
IPO review can proceed.
And therefore, everyone must understand
that this is not an individual's
problem, but a problem that the entire
system must face and solve together,
right? So, next I will discuss the most
crucial point, right? The
rectification requirements, right? So,
let me take a look.
Aha, so [clears throat]
right.
So, currently the review department has
given clear restrictions. All users must
complete account compliance processing
and tax payment within 5 days. So, the
uniform standard is tax payment of 12%
of the account balance, right? So, for
example, if your account has 50,000
dollars, you will need to pay 6,000
for the tax. So, this is currently the
most core and critical step in the
entire
rectification process. So, of course,
many people will ask a question, why
can't it be deducted directly from the
account?
So, I must clarify this point because
this review is led by an external audit
department,
and uh
they require complete data that is
verifiable,
traceable, and recordable, of course.
So,
if the platform deducts money directly
from the account, it cannot
form an independent payment record from
an auditing perspective, [clears throat]
right? So, in other words, the auditing
department cannot confirm
did you voluntarily pay this money or
has the tax payment been genuinely
completed, right? So, without an
independent record, this data is invalid
in an audit and will not be accepted,
unfortunately. So, therefore, this time
complete chain must be formed
through
user self-payment plus system record, so
that the auditing department can verify
and approve it
uniformly. This is not due to
complicated procedures, but rather the
capital market's basic requirement for
data all authenticated. So, regarding
another concern, the funds,
the fees paid this time are not lost,
nor other platform revenue. So,
after rectification this complete
completed, right? So,
and the audit is approved, these fees
will be processed processed by DSX and
refunded according to the tax paid.
So, um
that is to say, the funds you paid
during the rectification period can be
withdrawn normally after the audit is
completed. So, during the
rectification period, to ensure data
consistency, the platform will do two
things. First, suspend the withdrawal
function, unfortunately, then second,
suspend all trading services.
>> [sighs]
>> This isn't about restricting anyone, but
about ensuring all data remains
consistent and controllable during the
review process, right? So,
and once the rectification is completed,
and the review is passed, all functions
will return to normal. And finally, I
want to emphasize a crucial point any
exchange
want to enter the capital market must do
one thing, be open, transparent, and
compliant. So,
what are you experiencing now is a
necessary stage in a platform's journey
from internal growth to capital market
access. So, I hope everyone will
approach this with understanding, not
emotion.
And once the platform passes the
the hurdle, it will provide
a more stable, secure, and of course,
valuable environment. So,
of course, this isn't about just solving
problems. It's about laying a foundation
for our future
together. So, my final thought is for
everyone that is isn't a time to choose,
but
a time to cooperate, not a time to
observe, but a time to execute, of
course.
So,
basically, let's
all together let's navigate this stage
together, and the future will
truly belong to us as usual. Thank you.