Greetings, hello, hello from
this is Steven so I never left you back
or something like that so please be rest
assured because I'm here with you and I
totally understand this
right now we're in a very difficult
phase and we have to face some
difficulties as well so but please be
assured everything will be text
and calculated properly and everybody
will have money on the balance soon
enough this month you know just the
recent days
Also I would like to emphasize that I do
understand that DSJ's approach because
of course main interest of the company
is the first place yeah but
please do not worry try to be problem
oriented right not do not let any
emotions
to overcome you all right so next um
as for the
weekly zoom meeting I'll pass this this
time because we have more important
things to do
and I have to be concentrated on
these issues that appeared
so in any case
please
maintain order just wait patiently and
also the most important one
I you definitely need to follow the bone
chat official account right so our
groups and everything because the most
essential and important information will
be revealed there
and after all please do not answer any
because our enemies are trying to use
this disadvantage to their advantage
right now so in any case you must not
reply to their personal messages or
something like that from me from Alida
or anyone else
just try to concentrate on the bone chat
follow the
instructions and everything should be
fine and normal just well it's not the
first time for BGL sharing to face
difficulties like that
but definitely we'll overcome them just
like we did before so please maintain
order be patient
and just follow the group that's it all
the essential and most reliable
information
the only reliable information will be
over there so please do not worry about
anything just
be calm just like me I'm also trying to
be calm I understand it's not easy you
have anxiety
and worries but in any case um
we definitely supposed to maintain order
here just have to wait until the tax
station and everything is going through
the procedures and after all
we've been through so many
times I would like just to say a few
good words to you
um
we even had a birth of things on our
path before
but right now in this time it's also a
regular check of our occasion and our
structure and our
um
belief
so please
once again maintain order I'm here I
never left so I'm still fighting for you
so everything will be
normal just please try to take give give
it some time the problems will be solved
soon enough and everybody will be
uh holding their
withdrawals you'll be able to withdraw
your money so just soon enough just be
patient and after all please do not
hesitate to reach our official accounts
if you do encounter any problems so our
staff is doing everything possible
to maintain order and to
solve all these problems and
difficulties we have now so please
stay with me you stay believe and um
do not hesitate to reach us out all
right
more information you know the better but
please do not let any surrounding voices
to overcome
the normal procedures which we actually
given to you through the bone chat all
right please do not forget bone chat is
our everything so we need to follow it
in order to
um get the best results all right so
please just give us some time thank you
very much for your attention
unfortunately this meeting like I said
is not going to be holded this um
this week but we'll proceed it to the
next time
first
the priority here is just to solve these
problems we have now once they're solved
we're back to normal so please be
patient as always like I'm always trying
to and stay with us thank you so much
bye